Giving Back To Teachers

Log in with school email or use the name that comes with google. Allow nickname since teachers can see this. Everything should be saved under google IDs
After you log in you need to enter your school and grade.

Populate as you go website

Show what will be identifiable by teachers

Create grid that self populates as you move on

Add School: Name, Blocks

Add Teacher: Name, Subject, type(core, elective), class  name, email

On the top you have periods then beneath that you have
Subjects
Teachers
Note by student
Block
Thing they liked the most about their class
Project they liked the most or can remember

Nominations:
Easiest to approach
Most lenient with grades
Best about staying on topic
Best about actually teaching
Best about giving the right amount of work consistently
Best about making it easy to find homework
Most creative
Most planned
Nominations are done on a per student basis
These nominations should be first done by school then done by grade.

This will be done with node js using json as a database
Counting will happen as students go and if they change their mind they can just go back to the website and change anything.
Everything should save on the press of a button or maybe autosave if it’s easy.
A few graphics would be nice and maybe something different for each nomination 
More custom pictures will be necessary. (Either ask someone or make them you lazy fool)

After this there should be an easy way to share this website with a friend with an email address or send it using the @shoryamalani mail.

Everything needs to work without a human so its scalable. 

Send emails to teachers only and only if there are more than 5 students.(This counters trolls)
Send them all on a certain day.

Add a link to the contact page and add more to that
Add more to the home page
Work on colors in the website and how stuff is formatted









